

E: hello@anginno.com

W: anginno.com

P: 0449165098

A: 1808/163 City Rd, Southbank, 3006

About me

I am both a UX/UI Designer and front-end web developer with some skills in back-end. When it comes to designing sites and apps, I always put the user first to ensure the product has great user experience. I am a graduate with nearly a year's worth of experience and wanting to expand my skills and knowledge in web development further.

Education

Feb 2018 - Current

Bachelor of design (UX Design) Co-majoring in Computer Science Swinburne University of Technology

Feb 2017 - Dec 2017

Diploma of Digital Media Tech

Swinburne University of Technology

Feb 2016 - Dec 2016

Certificate IV in Digital Media Tech

Swinburne University of Technology

Technical Skills

Web development

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.js, JQuery PHP, SQL, Wordpress, bootstrap

UX/UI Design

Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, User testing, User research, responsive design.

Hobbies

Video games Playing guitar Board Games Soccer

Work Experience

Dec 2019 - Feb 2020

Front-end web developer and UX/UI Designer Scriibi

- Redesigned the site
- Conducted user testing sessions
- Developed front-end site using Laravel and bootstrap framework as a team
- Worked closely with back-end developers

Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

Full Stack developer and UX/UI Designer

TravelDialysisReview

- Designed website using figma
- Presented design and feature implementations to client
- Developed back-end with PHP and SQL
- Developed front-end of pages with bootstrap responsive framework

Volunteering

Nov 2018

Swinburne's GradX Volunteer

Supervised exhibition displays, attended exhibition catalogue table and directed guests around the exhibition.

Oct 2011

Flood relief volunteer

In Bangkok, I volunteered to help make sandbags in Suvarnabhumi airport to prevent further flooding in the city.

References

Matthew Raw

Team Leader/Traveldialysisreview

David NicolaidesDigital Lead/Scriibi

mattahraw@gmail.com 0400 357 077 david@scriibi.com 0415 373 670